<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chicago Tourist Guide</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Must Visit</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Towers</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Restaurants</string>

    <string name="info_art_institute">No visit to Chicago is complete without a trip to the Art Institute, the crown jewel in the city’s cultural scene. The museum has more than 300,000 works in its permanent collection, spanning many different movements such as the Renaissance and Surrealism. Expect to see quintessential pieces by Edward Hopper, van Gogh, Picasso, Monet and Cézanne, plus a vast array of sculptures, ceramics and contemporary pieces. It also boasts a stellar selection of rotating exhibitions that are well worth checking into ahead of your trip to plan accordingly. Book a fast-pass ticket before arriving to skip the lines.</string>
    <string name="info_mus_science">As one of the largest science museums in the world, the Museum of Science and Industry meticulously curates every installation, exhibit and showcase to pique curiosity and inquiry. Housed in a building constructed during the World’s Columbian Exposition in 1893, this vast institution offers an immersive experience into history, technology and the natural world. Exhibits include Science Storms, U-505 Submarine: 75 Stories, Coal Mine, Numbers in Nature: A Mirror Maze and more. Check out the website to purchase tickets and find details on the seasonal programming and exhibits.
</string>
    <string name="info_shedd">The Shedd Aquarium is home to approximately 32,000 animals, including sea otters, sharks, frogs, penguins and beluga whales, not to mention a multitude of different fish and coral species. The aquarium is divided into different geographical exhibits and offers a comprehensive daily schedule that includes spotlight sessions on various species, live dives and feedings, along with look-and-learn experiences. With so many activities and programming, this is easily a full-day excursion. Buying tickets in advance is strongly recommended.
</string>
    <string name="info_zoo">Lincoln Park Zoo is a 35 acre (14 ha) zoo in Lincoln Park, Chicago, Illinois. The zoo was founded in 1868, making it one of the oldest zoos in North America. It is also one of a few free admission zoos in the United States.[5] The zoo is an accredited member of the Association of Zoos and Aquariums (AZA).
Lincoln Park Zoo is home to a wide variety of animals. The zoo\'s exhibits include big cats, polar bears, penguins, gorillas, reptiles, monkeys, and other species totaling about 1,100 animals from some 200 species. Also located in Lincoln Park Zoo is a burr oak tree which dates to 1830, three years before the town of Chicago was incorporated</string>

    <string name="info_skydeck">One of the many things Chicago excels at is offering its visitors awe-inspiring 360-degree views of the city. For this reason alone, the Willis Tower’s renowned Skydeck is a must-visit. Located on the building’s 103rd floor 1,353 feet (412 meters) above the city, it’s the tallest spot to sightsee in Chicago – short of taking a helicopter ride. An ideal locale for an Instagram snap or two, the Skydeck provides views that are breathtaking from every angle – including down. As it’s hugely popular, expect long lines for this experience.
</string>

    <string name="info_trump">The Trump International Hotel and Tower is a skyscraper condo hotel in downtown Chicago, Illinois. The building, named after businessman and the 45th U.S. President Donald Trump, was designed by architect Adrian Smith of Skidmore, Owings and Merrill. Bovis Lend Lease built the 98-story structure, which reaches a height of 1,388 feet (423.2 m) including its spire, its roof topping out at 1,171 feet (357 m). It is next to the main branch of the Chicago River, with a view of the entry to Lake Michigan beyond a series of bridges over the river. The building received publicity when the winner of the first season of The Apprentice reality television show, Bill Rancic, chose to manage the construction of the tower over managing a new Trump National Golf Course and resort in Los Angeles.</string>

    <string name="info_john">875 North Michigan Avenue, formerly the John Hancock Center, is a 100 story, 1,128 foot supertall skyscraper located in Chicago, Illinois. Located in the Magnificent Mile district, its name was changed to 875 North Michigan Avenue on February 12, 2018.
It was constructed under the supervision of Skidmore, Owings and Merrill, with Colombian-Peruvian chief designer Bruce Graham and Bangladeshi structural engineer Fazlur Rahman Khan. When the building topped out on May 6, 1968, it was the second tallest building in the world and the tallest outside New York City. It is currently the fourth tallest building in Chicago and the ninth-tallest in the United States, after One World Trade Center, the Willis Tower, 432 Park Avenue, the Trump Tower Chicago, the Empire State Building, the Bank of America Tower, 30 Hudson Yards and the Aon Center. When measured to the top of its antenna masts, it stands at 1,500 feet (457 m). The building is home to several offices and restaurants, as well as about 700 condominiums. It also contains the third highest residence in the world, after the Burj Khalifa in Dubai and the Trump Tower in Chicago. The building was named for John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company, a developer and original tenant of the building. In 2018, John Hancock Insurance requested that its name be removed and the owner is seeking another naming rights deal.</string>

    <string name="info_tribune">The Tribune Tower is a neo-Gothic skyscraper located at 435 North Michigan Avenue in Chicago, Illinois, United States. Built between 1923 and 1925, the international design competition for the tower became an historic event in 20th century architecture.
The tower was the home of the Chicago Tribune, Tribune Media, and Tribune Publishing. WGN Radio (720 kHz) originated broadcasts from the building until moving to 303 Wacker Drive in June, 2018. The last WGN Radio broadcast emanated from the Tribune Tower on June 18, 2018. The ground level houses the large restaurant Howells and Hood (named for the building\'s architects), whose patio overlooks nearby Pioneer Court and Michigan Avenue. CNN\'s Chicago bureau was also located in the building. It is listed as a Chicago Landmark and is a contributing property to the Michigan–Wacker Historic District. The original Tribune Tower was built in 1868, but was destroyed in the Great Chicago Fire in 1871. In early 2018, work began on converting the entire office building into condominiums, expected to be completed by 2020.</string>

    <string name="euroasia">Very Delicious kyrgyz cuisine restaurant in the heart of the Chicago! Kosh Kelipsizder</string>
    
    <string name="tortazo">Chicago is no stranger to the culinary wonders that chef Rick Bayless can pull off - one look at his portfolio of local spots proves it (from Frontera Grill and Topolobampo to Lena Brava and Xoco). Last month he amped that number up to 11 with Tortazo, a fast-casual concept rooted in Mexican flavors and ingredients and housed within the city\’s iconic Willis Tower. Line up on the daily for lunch or dinner to sample through griddle-crisped tortas, chilaquiles, handcrafted bowls, and seasonal salads, all of which reflect the team\’s dedication to Latin cuisine by way of components like habanero pepper salsa, Cotija cheese, cilantro crema, and beyond. Do, of course, save room for dessert - the piping hot churro bites, rolled in cinnamon-sugar and topped off with Cajeta caramel, can\’t be missed</string>
    
    <string name="lula">This OG Logan Square favorite was embracing the farm-to-table philosophy long before it was cool, and has remained one of the North Side\’s most in-demand weekend brunch destinations since opening in 1999. The menu is subject to change depending on the seasonal availability of certain ingredients, but \"The Royale\" breakfast sandwich, which is currently made with turkey leg confit, Gruyere cheese, braised bacon, parsley salad, and a sunny-side egg on sourdough, is a sure bet.</string>
    
    <string name="bellemore">Former Bohemian House chef Jimmy Papadopoulos is back in the restaurant game and has teamed up with Boka Restaurant Group to resurrect the long-vacant Embeya space. While BoHo showcased Papadopoulos\' penchant for Eastern European flavors and cooking techniques, the menu here proves his versatility: a savory oyster custard flirts with Osetra caviar, creme fraiche, lemon dressed apple, and dill in the inventive oyster pie, dry-aged duck is glazed with raspberry vinegar and teamed with duck heart en crepinette, and venison tartare balances earthy grilled mushrooms with pumpernickel and lime. In addition, the restaurant also offers a six-course tasting menu for those who want to take the guesswork out of their meal.</string>
    <string name="title_choose">Open with</string>
    <string name="def_text">Nurmukhamed</string>
</resources>
